
[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///C:/Users/genya/Downloads/MyGemma3N/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html

Deprecated Gradle features were used in this build, making it incompatible with Gradle 9.0.

You can use '--warning-mode all' to show the individual deprecation warnings and determine if they come from your own scripts or plugins.

For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/8.13/userguide/command_line_interface.html#sec:command_line_warnings in the Gradle documentation.
